♪ ♪ [ woman vocalizing ]
[ woman screams ]
[ man laughing maniacally ]
[ ticking sound ]
[ boy panting ]
[ panting continues ]
[ woman ] Billy !
[ man laughing ]
[ ticking ]
[ loud breathing ]
[ man laughing ]
[ distorted voices ] [ man laughing ]
- [ ticking continues , louder ] - [ distorted voices , louder ]
- [ door opens ] - Bill ?
- [ boy ] It 's like a nightmare . - [ man ] Last night ?
My life .
[ man ] Are you scared ?
- I get scared . - Of what ?
My parents , um , my sister .
You .
Why ?
I don 't know why .
I-I feel like something 's going to happen ...
And if I scratch the surface , there 'll be something terrible underneath .
It 's perfectly normal ...
to experience a certain irrational fear in youth .
It 's no more than a stage .
And it will pass , I assure you .
[ man laughs maniacally ]
[ woman ] ♪ When you get tired of winning ♪
♪ When you get tired of pain ♪
♪ Or when your head is spinning ♪
♪ And you 've drunk all the best champagne ♪
♪ Then we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ To society we 'll be true ♪ [ distorted laughing ]
♪ Society waits for you ♪
♪ Oh , how we all get richer ♪
♪ Playing the ruling game ♪
♪ Only the poor get poorer ♪
♪ We feed on them all the same ♪
♪ Then we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ To society we 'll be true ♪
♪ Society waits for you ♪
[ louder ] ♪ Then we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ To society we 'll be true ♪
♪ Then we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ Society waits for you ♪
♪ We 'll all sing together ♪ ♪ [ fades ]
[ boy talking , indistinct ]
[ boy ] Come on . Come on .
Come on . Come and get it . Come and get it , Milo !
Is that confidence , or what ?
A matter of good breeding , Milo .
Yeah , you 're Mr. Perfect . You 'll probably end up assassinating the President .
You have one warped sense of humor , you know that ?
[ both laugh ]
[ together ] Blanchard .
Jenny ?
What ?
Blanchard 's here .
Damn it , Bill . You know I can 't see him .
Will you get rid of him for me , please ?
What are brothers for , huh ?
Milo .
- [ screaming ] - Jenny ... [ continues , indistinct ]
No ! Let go of me ! I 'm sorry about this . I didn 't mean to ...
- Just give me a minute . I can explain this . - Go away !
Listen to me !
What the hell do you think you 're doing , huh ?
- Bill , I know how this probably looks . - Get out of here .
[ Blanchard ] All right . Look ...
- Something very weird is going on here . - No shit , Sherlock .
[ Blanchard ] I have to talk to you .
- I didn 't know you had to hide in a closet to talk . - She 's playing games with me .
- [ Blanchard ] I 'm serious . - [ Jenny ] Liar !
Jen ? Bill ?
David , why do you keep bothering my daughter ?
Mrs. Whitney , I-I just want to talk to her ...
- Please , please . - Just ... just leave .
Come on , Blanchard .
Look , I ...
What 's going on here , guys ?
Oh , it was nothing , Dad .
It 's okay , Daddy .
I thought we weren 't going to be seeing David Blanchard anymore .
Yes , Daddy .
You should be getting ready . You know Judge Carter will be there tonight .
I 'm almost ready now .
Oh , Bill . Wasn 't that Milo outside ?
Uh , yeah . Yeah , he was just going to take me to the ...
the game .
- You okay ? - Sure .
So you want to tell me what 's going on with Blanchard ?
I don 't know . Jealous , I guess . He just wasn 't the right sort for me .
Could you zip me up , Billy ?
Something wrong ?
Uh , no . No , it 's just a little damp , that 's all .
Well , I 'm not taking another shower .
Yeah .
Look , I 'm-I 'm really sorry that I 'm going to miss your coming out .
What a coincidence the way things turn out , huh ?
Yeah . Come on . Basketball 's much more important than a stupid coming-out party .
Besides , I 've already been dating three years . Joke .
Yeah .
[ girl ] We are number one .
We are number one .
- All right ! - [ students cheering ]
Let 's hear it for the best player ,
our hero , Bill Whitney .
- All right ! Isn 't he wonderful ? - [ students cheering ]
Eat your heart out , girls .
We are number one ! Whoo !
They 're using their athletic ability to get the votes ...
- Of the childish morons in this audience . - [ students booing ]
Looks to me like you just lost the moron vote , Marty .
All right . Hey ! Let 's carry on with the debate .
[ Milo ] Candidate Whitney , you may respond concerning the proposed dress code .
[ student shouting , indistinct ]
Yeah . Well ...
- [ boy ] Hello ? - [ girl ] Come on .
We should have a dress code , I guess .
And I think we should follow it , and ...
- [ students murmuring ] - [ bill ] Most possible ...
Strict ...
- We poss ... we possibly can . - [ boy ] Speak up !
[ girl ] Louder !
[ students laughing ]
What I mean is , if we could prove to the administration ...
that a dress code really is a problem ...
I mean , just imagine everybody walking around in those idiotic clothes ...
like Marty over here is wearing right now .
And I mean everybody .
It 'd make them think that they were some kind of a ... a conspiracy .
She 's bad news , man .
[ chuckling ] The debate and the game .
I nailed the guy who was a shoo-in for the election .
Well , I 'm glad to see you 're allowing yourself some success without sabotaging it .
Let me ask you ,
how do you feel about your family now , in light of all these recent victories ?
- My family ? - Yes .
Um ...
Nothing .
I mean , I don 't think about them , they don 't think about me .
We 're just ... we 're just one big happy family .
- ' Cept for a little incest and psychosis . - [ man laughs ]
Look , I know you 're being facetious ,
but I think you really believe that .
No . No , I don 't . I don 't .
But we 're getting along much better now . Really .
Hey .
Let 's not waste our time bullshitting .
All right , all right .
They don 't approve of me , okay ? Th-they don 't accept my friends .
They don 't talk to me like they do Jenny .
Hell , they don 't even look like me .
Now I told you that teenagers sometimes feel alienated from those closest to them .
Alienated .
- I think I was adopted . - [ chuckles ]
- Don 't you think that sounds a little bit paranoid ? - No .
No , I 've never been paranoid .
Just a little bit paranoid , Bill .
Within normal ranges .
You know , you really deserve what 's going to happen to you .
What 's going to happen ?
You 're going to make a wonderful contribution to society .
♪ ♪ [ classical ]
Jenny ? Hey , I need some suntan lotion .
♪ ♪ [ continues ]
Jenny ?
- Jenny ? - [ water running ]
[ soft moaning ]
Listen , Jenny , I 'm just go ...
[ moaning ]
God , Bill ! What 's the matter with you ?
Get out of here !
Uh , Jenny ... I 'm sorry , really . I just came in here to get this .
Get out of here .
- [ both laughing ] - Rocky , that 's beautiful .
[ continues , indistinct ]
- That 's the most incredible crop we 've ever raised . - I know .
[ Mom ] Rocky , you 've done a terrific job .
Bill ?
There he is . The future Student Body President of Beverly Hills Academy .
We 're so excited about our party for Judge Carter next week .
- Well , um , I 'm gonna go go to the beach today . - Oh .
When will you be back , son ?
- Well , that depends on if we go out after ... - Don 't be late , darling .
Oh , I love that one . Look at that , it 's really good .
- This is the best crop you 've ever grown , rocky . - Absolutely perfect .
[ squeaking sound ]
[ laughing ]
I love you , you know .
And if you really love me ,
you 'll get us invited to Ted Ferguson 's party .
I can 't believe we were left out .
Look , he 's over there .
Come on , Billy baby , couldn 't you go talk to him ?
Please ?
- Die , aliens , die ! - Hey !
- Hey , hey ! Jesus , goddamn it ! - My hair !
Give me that ! Hey !
[ spitting out sand ] Hey ! Hey , get back here .
Don 't get too hot .
[ angry sigh ]
Hey ! It 's Whitney the Wonder Boy .
Come here . Is this part of the beach dress code ?
Hope you 're not bent out of shape .
After all , I am the Captain of the Debating Team .
Hey , nothing you do can bend me .
Just remember , Whitney , we don 't lose .
What are you gonna do , rig the election or something ?
I don 't have to . Martin here was born to lead .
So , uh , you know of anything that 's going on this week ?
- This week ? - [ snickers ]
I can 't think of anything .
- Well , if you do , let me know , huh ? - I 'll send you a telegram .
[ girl laughing ]
- Yeah , let me know , huh ? - It 's my pleasure .
- Bill ? [ Panting ] - Hey , Blanchard . What 's up ?
I 've got something you gotta hear .
- You were out of line with my sister . - Oh , God , no . Look .
I 'm serious . This is very important . [ panting ]
- What are you talking about ? - Look , not here .
Just come with me to the pier , okay ? Please ?
Come on .
I think what you 'll find in paragraph ten will excite ...
- Dad , something 's wrong with one of my earrings . - Oh , Jenny .
Oh , hello , Judge Carter . How is our newest confirmed member of society ...
- this lovely afternoon ? - Oh , I 'm fine . It 's my earring that 's not doing so well .
I must say , young lady , you certainly added beauty ...
to an altogether beautiful coming-out party , don 't you agree , Jim ?
Prettiest girl there , your honor . Please , be seated .
It 's right in the back by the clasp .
Oh , yes . There seems to be something caught in there .
Top secret , eh , Blanchard ? [ chuckles ]
- [ Dad on tape ] Everybody in ? - [ Jenny ] Yes , Dad .
[ Dad ] All right , girls , don 't forget your seat belts .
Wait a minute . That 's my family .
All right , Bill . I know you 're going to be a little upset about this , but ,
I put a voice-actuated tape recorder underneath your parents ' car ...
- And a microphone in Jenny 's ear . - You bugged my family ?
- [ continues , indistinct ] - Just listen to the tape . Listen .
[ Mom ] I remember my own coming out . I was so excited .
[ Jenny ] Then you can do it with women as well as men ?
- [ Mom ] Of course . - [ Dad ] You know the schedule . First dine , then copulation .
Someone your own age first . Then with your mother and me .
Then in comes the host . You 'll be ready .
[ Jenny ] I could hardly keep a straight face when Bill apologized to me ...
- about not being able to make it . - Don 't be concerned about your brother , Jen .
He 's too busy with things in his own world to worry about ours .
[ clicks off , tape whirring ]
[ girl ] You lucked out , Jen . Ted Ferguson is really cute for a first partner .
- Ted Ferguson ? Ted Ferguson ! - Yeah , Jenny and Ferguson .
That 's just the beginning . Here , listen .
[ girl ] Wow , your boobs look totally sexy .
Guys are gonna pop high ones the second they see you .
- [ Jenny ] I 'm a little nervous , though . - [ girl ] It 's fun .
Relax , Jenny . Go with it . It 's so much fun to see how far you can stretch .
The hotter and wetter you get , the more you can do . It 's great !
- It 's a microphone . - Let me see .
David Blanchard 's been bothering my daughter recently .
Following her around . Things like that .
He 's a real electronics wizard .
Is that so , Jim ?
[ Jenny moaning ] Oh , Ted , you were wonderful .
[ man ] Don 't get too cocky , Ted . You know what I mean ?
[ Jenny ] Oh . Oh , Ted . Oh , my God .
- [ girl ] Whoa ! - [ Jenny ] Is that him ?
[ moaning , laughing continue ]
- [ man ] Hold on . What are you doing ? - [ girls laughing ]
- [ man yelling ] - [ girl laughing ]
- [ girl ] God , this is excellent . - [ man continues yelling ]
- What the hell are you doing ? - [ man screaming ]
Bill , now , come on .
It 's bullshit , man . You rigged it .
You 've been living with these people all your life and you didn 't know anything ?
Shut up !
- Give me this ! Give me ! - Bill !
- Blanchard ! - Come on . Don 't do it .
Come on . Here 's your stupid recorder .
Bill ? Wait !
[ door bell rings ]
- Dr. Cleveland , you gotta listen to this tape . - Something happen at home ?
- I 'm not crazy . This is real . I can 't believe it . - Uh ...
Well , I can 't right now , but I 'll be glad to listen to it later .
- No , no , now ! Please ? Please ? - Billy ?
Trust me , I will call you just as soon as I listen to it , or I 'll see you tomorrow .
- No , no , no . No . - It 's okay , Billy . Give me the tape .
You still don 't trust me ? Are you still afraid of me ?
Okay , it 's up to you , Billy . If you want to bring it tomorrow , that 's okay .
Look , I-I don 't know why I 'm afraid , but I ...
Doctor , it 's very important .
I understand .
Listen to it .
Okay , now listen . Yesterday , after you left the beach ,
I heard something .
It involved my parents , my sister and Ted Ferguson .
He 's not inviting us , is he ?
- I knew it . - Just listen to me for a minute here .
Stop worrying about that stupid party .
It may seem stupid to you , but I want to go .
Is that all you think about ? Parties and social status ?
If you 're having problems because you 're so big-headed and selfish ,
no wonder no one ever invites us anywhere .
I don 't believe this .
I 'm trying to tell you something and all you 're doing is giving me shit .
Oh ! Oh , fine , fine . That 's just fine .
If that 's how you feel about me , well , I 'm just glad I know it now rather than later .
I don 't know , Billy . Maybe we should start seeing other people .
Wait a minute . Shauna ? Shauna ? Shauna , wait ...
- Oh , man . - Hey , Bill ...
Milo .
Hey , dude , I see you got ...
I 'm very concerned about you , Billy .
- You listen to the tape ? - You 're aware , aren 't you , what you 're doing is illegal ?
What about what they were doing ?
My father and sister and my mother ...
Together .
- [ Dad ] Everybody in ? - [ Mom ] All in .
[ Dad ] All right , girls , don 't forget the seat belts .
Fast forward a little bit .
[ clicks , tape whirring ]
[ Mom ] I remember my own coming out . God , I was so excited .
[ Jenny ] You mean I can dance with anyone I want ?
- [ Mom ] Of course . - I-I don 't understand .
[ Dad ] You know the schedule . First we dine , then introductions .
Then you 'll be presented .
No . No . [ stammering ]
[ Jenny ] Oh , my God . It 's so exciting .
[ Dad ] Don 't worry , dear . We 'll be there to help you .
[ Jenny ] I felt bad that Bill couldn 't come . I hope he doesn 't feel left out .
[ Dad ] We 're very proud of your brother . It 's unfortunate that he couldn 't be with us .
That 's not what I heard .
[ clicks , tape whirring ]
- [ clicks ] - [ people laughing ]
Bill ?
Billy ,
people are what they are .
Now you have to learn to accept that .
And you have to learn to accept society 's rules of privacy .
If you don 't follow the rules , Billy , bad things happen .
Now some people make the rules , some people follow the rules .
It 's a question of what you 're born to .
- I really hate giving you drugs , Billy . - What ?
- I don 't believe this . - You can always trust me .
You 've got to believe me .
Blanchard ? Yeah , look , I need another copy of the tape .
- No , it can 't wait . Ple ... - Yeah , the corner of Roxbury and Wilshire , right .
Okay . Hurry , okay ? Hurry !
[ door slams ]
Blanchard .
[ police radio , indistinct ]
Is he dead ?
[ engine starts , tires squeal ]
[ dog barking in distance ]
Hey , this isn 't a garage sale .
- Look , officer , he was a friend . - Look ,
you can 't just wander into the scene of an accident .
- Look , officer , something is definitely wrong here . - Get the hell out of here .
- You don 't understand . - Get the hell out of here .
Guess what ? A telegram came for you .
Listen , Jenny , something bad happened today .
Oh , come on . Don 't you want to open it ?
Go ahead . Read it .
" Mr. William Whitney ,
" you 're cordially invited to a party given at the residence of Theodore S. Ferguson ...
Wow .
" This evening , the Fifteenth of October at 8 : 00 P.M.
Cordially , Ted ' The Tycoon ' Ferguson . "
Sounds like some bash , son .
But be careful on the drinking and driving .
Oh , that home is just beautiful .
Maurice Arnaud did most of the interiors , and he says it 's his best work to date .
Uh , um ...
You guys don 't understand . I 'm trying to tell you something .
We know all about the , um , the automobile accident , son .
- It 's terrible , just terrible . - Oh , my ... Just awful .
Wait a minute , I-I ...
I don 't think you quite understand here .
David 's dead .
- Jenny ? - I know . I 'm really going to miss him .
That 's it ? You 're really going to miss him ?
I know the guy freaked out after you dumped him , but , come on , still ...
Listen , I 'd rather not talk about it , please ?
So , what are you going to wear ?
- You mean to the funeral ? - No , you weirdo . To the Ferguson 's party .
Yeah , right . Ferguson .
- ♪ ♪ [ dance ] - [ people chattering ]
[ girl laughing ] Yeah , come on .
[ chattering fades ]
- You 're name is Clarisa , isn 't it ? - Mm-hmm .
Clarisa Carlyn .
So where 's Shauna ?
Well , I didn 't expect to see her here , if that 's what you mean .
That is who you go with , right ?
- Do you know my Mom 's maiden name too ? - Real or adopted ?
Bill . Bill , what happened with Blanchard ?
Milo . Ferguson invited you ?
Come on . Give me a break . I 'm not in the mood , all right ?
- Whatever turns you on . - At least I don 't turn tricks to get my kicks .
Oh , Milo .
- That was totally uncalled for . - Have you seen her mother ?
Wait , wait . Listen , listen . What happened today with Blanchard ?
Hey , I asked you about Blanchard . You saw it , didn 't you ?
I can 't deal with that right now , okay ? I gotta go .
Well , Billy .
We need to talk .
Guess you got my telegram . Sorry it was so much at the last minute .
I wanna talk to you about Blanchard and my sister , Jenny .
I thought they broke up .
He wasn 't really her type anyway .
Don 't be so intense .
Just relax . Enjoy .
I want to know what happened to Blanchard .
And I want to know what you did to my sister at her coming out .
You know the schedule . First we dined ,
then I fucked your sister ,
then everybody else got so turned on , they fucked her too .
And as far as bagel-breath Blanchard goes ,
I ran that low-rent fool right into a pole .
That 's a pretty busy week , don 't you think ?
You are stupid !
You make waves , Whitney , you 're going to drown .
[ guests laughing ]
- [ girl ] Hey , let 's go . - [ boy ] That 's a stupid place to fall .
Wet dreams ?
You 're crazy . You know what you just did ?
No . But I know what I 'm about to do .
Don 't bother . It 's his party .
Someday , it 's going to be my party .
You know ,
you 're in danger of losing this button here .
It 's only held on by one thread .
Oops . Told you .
- You 're weird . - Wanna go get soaked ?
- Well , sure . - [ laughs ]
Better get out of these wet things .
Mmm . You seem so fresh .
Uh , are you sure no one 's going to come in ?
I 'm all alone .
[ giggles ] Lean machine , jelly bean .
Try to run now .
Clarisa ?
What 's the matter , Billy ?
You , uh , you were in a funny position .
Oh , Billy . You 're so sweet .
I wonder when exactly you lost your virginity . [ Giggles ]
- See , that 's Bill 's Jeep . - It is . I can 't believe he would do this to me .
Oh , come on , Shauna . It 's better you find out now rather than later , right ?
- Wrong . - God , what a bitch that Clarisa Carlyn is .
- Can you imagine what 's going on ? - All right , all right .
How do your like you tea ? Cream ? Sugar ? Or do you want me to pee in it ?
[ scoffs ] You 're a class act , Clarisa .
Oh , I 'm so mad I could just scream .
- Who 's that ? - I don 't know .
- We better get out of here . - Mm-hmm .
Oh , shit . Clarisa ? Clarisa ?
Home a little early tonight , don 't you think so , mother ?
Has that brain of yours finally gone completely numb ?
[ gagging ]
- Mrs. Carlyn , Bill Whitney . - [ continues gagging ]
Come on , mother . Out !
Out !
Clarisa , what are you doing ?
Lighten up , Billy boy . Drink your tea before you drool .
So what 's with her ?
She does things I don 't like .
I 've never known anyone like you .
It 's about time you did , honey bunny .
It 's getting late .
[ dog barking in distance ]
- Shauna ? - So are you happy now ?
- What do you mean ? - What a bitch that Clarisa Carlyn is .
You think that you can do anything you want and get away with it .
- Look , just calm down and let me explain . - Was she a good fuck ?
Because that 's all you 're really interested in . Isn 't it , Billy ?
No , look , Shauna , let ... um ...
Oh , Billy , how could you ?
Uh , look , I ...
Shauna !
[ engine starts ]
Yeah , right there , Dad . That 's good .
- What 's this ? - Oh , God , bill .
Is that what I think it is ?
That 's a really disgusting thing to bring into Mom and Dad 's bedroom .
I don 't know what 's going on here , but I don 't appreciate it .
- Calm down , Bill . - Some of us have to get to school on time .
You know , you look really nice in a tie .
Don 't you think so , Jim ?
Yes , yes he does .
Knock it off here !
Why ? Why are you guys doing this to me , huh ?
- Don 't be so paranoid . - Wait ...
- I 'm not paranoid . - Don 't be like that .
Come on , Bill . Now calm down .
You know , you 'll make such a great contribution to society .
You 'll ... you 'll do our whole family proud .
Man , you guys disgust me .
- Wha ... - Bill , don 't be disrespectful to your mother .
My mother ? God knows where my mother is .
I won 't tolerate this language from you , young man .
Fuck you , butthead .
Bill ! How dare you use the " F " word to your father .
Oh , gee , I 'm sorry , Mom . Prefer the word , copulation ?
[ gasps ]
You stay away from me . Don 't touch me .
[ Mom ] Do something with him .
You don 't have to do anything anymore , because I 'm moving out .
You can 't do that .
[ bill ] Blanchard .
He looks really weird . Not like himself at all .
I think that 's what they always look like .
They , um , must have had to do a lot of reconstructive stuff on him .
- Yeah . - Yeah .
- Bill ? It 's imperative that I talk with you . - [ Gasps ]
It 's about your parents ,
about him ,
about some of the things that have been happening here lately .
Society .
- What-what do you mean , society ? - Not here .
Meet me tonight at Franklin Canyon , about 9 : 00 , at the gate .
Wait a minute . Petrie ?
Petrie ? Hey !
[ engine starts ]
Petrie !
Hey ? Petrie ? Hey .
[ cracking sound ]
Who 's there ?
[ gasps ] Oh !
[ grunts ]
- [ man laughing ] - [ footsteps receding ]
Who are you ?
[ gasps , grunts ]
- Clarisa , what are you doing here ? - I live here .
Yeah , look , I just saw Petrie with his neck cut .
Poor baby . I hope he didn 't make a mess .
Where 's your phone , huh ?
This isn 't the one .
I don 't think we need the lab to tell us there 's no blood .
Look , officer , this isn 't the car .
They-they must have taken it . I don 't know .
They ? What are you hopped up on ?
Look , I 'm telling you , someone killed Martin Petrie .
Up against the car , kids .
Look , this isn 't the car , okay ?
It was a Volvo , not whatever this is . There was a dead person in it .
Is it really that boring being rich ?
You going to frisk me too ?
I guess you 're just naturally fucked up , huh ?
Next time I see you , it will be a lot less pleasant .
What now ? You can go home with me .
- I 'm not in the mood , all right ? - That 's not what I meant .
- [ boy ] All right . - [ banging sound ]
All right . Hey !
We 'll begin the Presidential Debate in a Moment .
Bill , why didn 't you come home last night ? Mom and Dad are really upset .
Jenny , do you have anything to tell me ?
What do you want me to say ?
Come on . I swear ... I swear it 'll be just between you and me .
Just-just tell me the truth .
- About what ? - You know what .
Bill , I 'm really worried about you .
[ sighs ] Yeah . Sure you are .
[ Milo ] All right , quiet down .
Thank you .
Where 's Petrie ?
It 's strange that Martin Petrie isn 't here . He 's never late .
He 's won every attendance award .
- But he 's not coming here . - [ students murmuring ]
No , please .
David-David Blanchard 's death was no accident .
David Blanchard tried to tell me about the society that kills ...
To keep its existence a secret .
They killed Blanchard .
Martin Petrie tried to tell me about-about this society ,
but they got to him before I did .
I saw Petrie ,
last night in Franklin Canyon ... murdered .
- [ all gasping ] - [ student ] What ?
Martin Petrie is dead .
[ students laughing ]
Would someone like to tell me what 's going on here ?
- I had car trouble . - [ laughter increases ]
Nice speech , Whitney . [ laughing ]
Bill ...
- Bill ? Bill , we gotta talk . - Leave me alone , Milo .
I fucked you up , man , and I 'm sorry . I didn 't think you 'd take it this far .
What do you mean ?
I mean , I was the one who put the shrunken head in your locker ...
And the sex doll in your Jeep , but I didn 't think you 'd flip out .
You ! You , Petrie , Ferguson .
Who else was in on this , huh ? Who else , asshole ?
Just give me a chance to explain . I 'm trying to tell you ,
you crazy son of a bitch , but you got your own answers , as usual .
I 'm not in on anything , but I followed you to Franklin Canyon last night .
I saw Petrie and Ferguson coming out of the woods . Petrie was wrapped in a blanket .
Then some old station wagon showed up . Then an old Ford .
The whole thing was weird .
You-you saw it ?
I only followed you because of the way you were acting .
Wait a minute . Then-then it 's not me . I 'm not going crazy .
Right .
Hey . Why the dolls and stuff ?
I don 't know . You just got me angry .
You know , I 'm your best friend when it suits you .
Guess I do go a little overboard .
- I 'm sorry . - [ chuckles ]
It 's all right , man . It 's all right .
Milo , I , uh ,
I don 't know what kind of trouble this is gonna be .
I 'm with you .
[ squeaks brakes , shuts off engine ]
[ car door slams ]
[ shuts off engine ]
[ crickets chirping ]
[ muttering ]
Why doesn 't it surprise me that you 're all here like this ?
Thank God you 're here . You nearly spoiled everything .
[ vehicle approaching ]
You know , we 've been worried sick about you .
Look , I would really love to stay and shoot the shit ,
but I got a big day tomorrow , so I 'm-I 'm gonna go to bed .
- [ gasps ] - No , wait .
No , wait a minute , Bill . We want to talk to you for a second .
I-I don 't think so . Wait , what are you doin ' ?
Let go of me . Let go !
- Bill . Bill . Bill ! - What do you think you 're doing ? What ?
I 'm sorry . You know how I hate to give you drugs .
You can 't do this to me . I have rights , okay ? I 'm almost 18 !
Thanks , Cleve .
[ hissing , increasing in volume ]
[ starts engine ]
[ doors , stretcher clattering ]
- [ woman on P.A. ] Maintenance ... - [ phone ringing ]
Excuse me . Miss !
Bill ... uh , William Whitney . What room 's he in ?
[ sighing ] Whitney .
I don 't see anything here about a Whitney .
[ sighs deeply ] I know he 's here . He was just brought in .
Well , just a minute .
- [ door opening , closing ] - [ woman on P.A. ] Dr. Oswald , 5493 .
Dr. Oswald , 5493 .
- William Whitney ? - Yeah .
- Are you a relative ? - Yes !
- Well , you have to go to the morgue , then . - The morgue ?
- Mm-hmm . - He isn 't dead ! He just got here .
- Well , I 'm sorry . - No , no , no !
No , no ! You 're not sorry , there 's been a mistake !
Now , please . We don 't want to have to call security .
He can 't be !
[ siren wailing ]
[ car door closing ]
- [ rushing sound ] - [ bill ] Blanchard , what 's up ?
[ Blanchard ] I 've got something you 've got to hear .
[ Dr. Cleveland ] I 'm sorry . You know how I hate to give you drugs .
[ Jenny ] He just wasn 't the right sort for me .
[ Dad ] You know the schedule . First we dine , then copulation .
- With someone your own age first . - [ ted ] Bill , I fucked your sister .
I mean , everybody else got so turned on , they fucked her too .
[ Mom ] You know you 'll make such a great contribution to society .
[ man , indistinct ] Do you know anything about this ?
[ boy ] Aah ! Aah ! No !
[ panting ] Blanchard ?
- [ boy ] No ! - [ clattering , struggling ]
- [ doctor ] Let 's get this one out of here . - [ nurse ] Yes , doctor .
- Easy , easy , easy . Hold this . - [ Boy ] Ow ! Ow !
- [ whimpering continues ] - Disconnect the cord . [ doctor continues , indistinct ]
[ grunting , retching ]
[ chuckles ]
[ chuckles ] That 's right , roll out the red carpet .
Bill Whitney never disappoints , huh ?
[ chortles ] Ha !
They said you were dead .
Things are just the way they seem .
Only more so , Milo .
- [ chuckles ] - What happened ?
- What did they do to you ? - Nothin ' !
I 'm here , aren 't I , huh ? I won , Milo . I 'm free .
They couldn 't handle Whitney the wonder boy . [ Laughing ]
Bullshit . It 's a setup !
- Look , they even brought your Jeep here . - Come on !
They just want me to be happy . [ giggles ]
Bill , you 're officially dead .
Come on ! Can 't you see they 're setting you up for something ?
Paranoid ? I 'm not paranoid . All my fears are real .
- Come on . - [ starting engine ]
Let 's party , jelly bean .
Hmm ? Where 's your Mom ?
- Or was she in on this too ? - Why don 't you come upstairs ?
I want to be a bad girl for you .
Oh , bad little girl . Is that right , huh ? Bad little girl ?
Oh . Huh ? You want to get rough ?
- Things aren 't the way they seem , Billy . - Oh , yeah ?
Why don 't you stay here awhile ?
- Stay here awhile . - [ panting ]
Quit it . It doesn 't work anymore .
- Don 't go home , Billy . - Don 't go home ?
Are you kidding ? They want me home !
It 's time to party hearty !
[ door opens , closes ]
Where are we going ? What 's the plan ?
Plan ? Are you kiddin ' ?
[ starts engine ]
Aah ! Shit !
[ grunts ] Mrs. Carlyn ! Don 't do that !
All right . Get out of the car .
[ gasps ]
Okay . We 're gonna take a little ride .
- [ slams door ] - But don 't touch the hair .
[ starts engine ]
[ woman grunts ]
[ man ] Shh !
- [ clicks light switch ] - [ rustling , distant shouting ]
[ whispering , indistinct ]
[ man , whispering ] Where did he go ?
- [ man , laughing ] - [ woman ] Shh !
[ man , whispering ] I hear him .
Mom ? Dad ?
[ beeping ]
- Fuck , Mom . - [ woman screaming ]
[ car doors closing ]
[ laughing , indistinct ]
[ man , whispering ] Keep it down .
[ panting , sighing ] Okay .
Mom ? Dad ?
I 'd like to have a little chat with you .
[ grunting , shouting ]
[ chattering , laughing ]
- [ Mom clapping ] - [ various people ] Yes , yes .
Wonderful . Wonderful !
Everyone was just wonderful .
[ woman ] Oh , thank you .
And now , ladies and gentlemen , Judge Carter .
[ choking , panting ]
- [ chuckling ] My dear , dear ... - Ohh .
Ah ! You were both absolutely brilliant .
- [ giggling ] - Oh , thank you .
Well done . Well done indeed .
Effective . Efficient .
- Oh ! - And , to say the very least , entertaining ?
[ crowd laughing ]
I do love the ... smell of the hunt .
And the taste of the shunt .
- What 's goin ' on ? - You see , Bill .
It 's like this :
[ chuckling ] There 's no business like show business .
[ all laughing ]
- Who are you ? - Oh , I am not your mother .
Jesus , Bill . You never were one of us . [ laughing ]
Who are you ?
You almost understand , don 't you , Bill ?
You 're a different race from us . A different species .
A different class .
You 're not one of us !
You have to be born in the society .
- Alien scum . - [ laughing ] No .
No , we 're not from outer space , or anything like that .
We have been here ... as long as you have .
It 's a matter of ...
good breeding , really .
- [ choking ] Alien scum ! - [ coughing ]
[ car approaching ]
[ car doors slamming ]
Good evening , miss .
[ chattering , chuckling ]
[ groaning ]
[ groaning continues ]
Clarisa ! Where have you been ?
You 're late ! Come .
You 've done very well , Jim .
I 'm pleased to be able to contribute .
Anything for society .
You too , young man . You have a bright future ahead of you .
We may have an internship for you this summer , in Washington .
[ chuckles , exhales ]
Come on .
Come on , Mrs. Carlyn . You 're gonna be my date .
Jenny 's going to Radcliffe . She 'll tour Europe first , of course .
Oh , Nanny , Nanny , you are such a lucky woman .
Jenny is a real beauty .
She possesses such ... natural poise .
[ chuckles ]
Yes , Jim and I both derive a great deal of pleasure from her .
- Don 't we , darling ? - [ clattering ]
[ whimpering , shouting ]
Ladies and gentlemen ,
tonight ... we have a doubleheader !
- Blanchard . - [ whispering ] Yeah .
[ raucous laughing ]
After the first shunting ,
we 'll have that special treat we 've been hearing so much about .
A wonderful specimen , in his prime ,
nurtured by Jim and Nan in their very own home .
[ laughing wickedly ]
[ Blanchard ] Get it off . Help !
[ groaning continues ]
[ gasps , chokes ]
Keep your eye on Blanchard , Billy boy ... ' cause you 're next .
[ Blanchard ] You 're hurting me !
What are you doing ?
[ sobbing ] Oh , God ! Please !
[ crowd growling , chattering ]
[ screams ] Let go of me !
[ slurping ]
[ Blanchard moaning ]
Jim ? Jenny ?
- [ Jenny ] Good-bye , David . - [ chuckles ]
- [ moaning ] - [ gagging ]
[ billy moaning ] Stop it !
You 're not getting a taste for these pathetic animals , are you ?
Don 't worry ! You 'll get your share .
We 're all gonna get our share .
- What the fuck 's going on ? - Didn 't you know , Billy boy ?
The rich have always sucked off low-class shit like you .
There it is . There 's the house .
Hey ! Hey , what are you doing in there ?
This is a private party . And private property . It 's members only .
- We 're invited ! - Oh , you 're invited ?
- Who 's that ? - This is my mother !
[ snorts ] That 's your ...
Hair ! Hair , Mrs. Carlyn !
[ guard ] Wait a minute ... [ groaning ]
[ chattering , chuckling ]
[ Cleveland ] He 's good and pliable , your honor !
[ woman laughing ]
Oh , my lord .
[ cackling ]
Oh , look . Look ! A beauty mark !
Pretty , isn 't it ?
Please .
- [ growls , munches ] - [ woman ] Ah , yes !
And now ,
we 'll get to the bottom ...
Oh , God !
- Of this ! - [ screaming ]
[ growling , moaning ]
[ laughing ] Whoo !
[ Clarisa ] Run , Billy !
I love you .
[ continues laughing ]
Billy !
[ Cleveland ] Where are you ?
[ chortling ] Where are you , Billy ?
Anyone around my base is " I-T , " it .
It 's show time , Billy !
You want to play , huh ? You want to play ?
[ laughing ]
[ panting ] You ! You !
[ chuckles wickedly ]
Let me give you a hand , Bill .
[ wicked laughter ]
- [ slurping , dripping sound ] - Mom ?
Oh , Billy .
How sweet of you ...
To come here to me !
- [ sighing ] - If you have any edible fantasies ...
you 'd like to indulge in , Billy , now 's the time .
[ laughing ]
[ flatulence ]
Uh , well , son , I guess you 're right .
I am a butthead . [ laughs hysterically ]
Hey , hey . Hey , Bill ? [ flatulence ]
[ laughing continues ]
[ screams ]
[ laughs ] It 's just another hang-up , Billy .
[ gurgling sound ]
♪ ♪ [ " Eton Boat Song , " instrumental ]
[ laughing , chattering ]
- No way ! - Ohh !
♪ ♪ [ continues ]
Stop it . I don 't want to ...
[ guffawing ] Hi-ho , everybody ! Here comes Billy !
Let go of me ! Stop !
Dinner is served . Billy on the half-shell !
Billy ...
Leave her alone !
[ scoffs ] Oh-ho , well , well , well .
Look what we have here . Are you going to rescue the young maiden , Billy ?
- Something like that . - [ chuckles ]
You and me , man-to-man .
[ giggles ] Well , well . A slave revolt .
[ continues laughing ]
I love it . You gotta save the girl . It 's so cute !
Billy , don 't ! You 'll only make it worse .
- Shut up , Clarisa . - Jim and Nan , where the hell are ya ?
[ digestive rumblings ]
[ bones cracking ]
[ coughing , gasping ]
I 've got to pull myself together .
A beauty mark . [ chuckles ]
[ coughs , chokes ]
I 'm getting too old for this .
Nan ! Jim ! Hey , come on , you guys !
Knock it off , will ya ? You have got to come downstairs .
- You 've got to see this ! - [ Jim ] Be right out .
- We 're changing . - Oh , really ? Into what ?
[ laughs uproariously ]
Members of society ...
hailing from Beverly Hills ,
with lineage dating from Julius Caesar ...
and Genghis Khan .
The Master of the Hunt , the Champion of the Shunt ...
Ted " The Tycoon " Ferguson !
[ cheering , applauding ]
And , in this corner ,
from nowhere in particular ,
Bill " The Bastard " Whitney .
Gentlemen , begin !
- Begin ! - [ crowd cheering , jeering ]
Is everybody ready for the big shunt of the night ?
Hey , Ferguson ...
[ billy grunts ]
- More ? More ? - Yeah , yeah , yeah !
Shunt him ! Shunt him ! Shunt the little bastard !
Bill ! Bill !
Bill !
See this arm , Bill ? You 'll get very familiar with it .
[ grunts ]
[ man ] Whoo-hoo ! C 'mon , boy !
Stop ! No !
[ shrieking ]
Shit ! [ Gagging ]
Is that all ya got ? Huh ?
Come on , Gumby . Give me your best sh ...
- [ grunts ] - All right , Billy . The game 's over .
I told you , Whitney . We don 't lose .
Ever . [ Slurping ]
Yes ! Don 't even touch him ! Goddamn !
[ man ] What 's going on ?
No !
[ groaning in pain ]
[ man ] No . No !
[ gurgling ]
[ girl ] God , he 's turned him inside out .
[ man ] Don 't touch it or you 'll be killed !
[ grunting ] Clarisa !
Bill ! Come on , man .
You 'll never get away with this .
[ whimpering ]
Don 't count on it .
Butthead .
Come on ! Come on !
Whoo !
[ Milo ] Get out of the way !
[ slurping sounds ]
[ judge ] Well , Dr. Cleveland .
It looks as though I may have an opening in Washington next summer .
- Know what I mean ? - Mm . Mm .
[ woman ] ♪ When you get tired of winning ♪
♪ When you get tired of fame ♪
♪ Or when your head is spinning ♪
♪ And you 've drunk all the best champagne ♪
♪ When we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ To society we 'll be true ♪
♪ Then we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ Society waits for you ♪
♪ Oh , how we all get richer ♪
♪ Playing the rolling game ♪
♪ Only the poor get poorer ♪
♪ We feed off them all the same ♪
♪ Then we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ To society we 'll be true ♪
♪ Society waits for you ♪
♪ ♪ [ continues , instrumental ]
♪ Some may call us sinners ♪
♪ Be thankful that 's all they 'll say ♪
♪ It 's done with such restraint ♪
♪ And we 'll all sing together ? ?
♪ To society we 'll be true ♪
♪ Society waits for you ♪
♪ ♪ [ instrumental ]
♪ Some will call us sinners ♪
♪ Be thankful that 's all they 'll say ♪
♪ Some may call us sinners ♪
♪ It 's done with such restraint ♪
♪ Then we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ To society we 'll be true ♪
♪ Then we 'll all sing forever ? ?
♪ Society waits for you ♪
♪ Then we 'll all sing together ♪
♪ To society we 'll be true ♪
♪ Society waits for you ♪ ♪